safecaller.com 2005-10-23

# National DO NOT CALL List Software Solutions

Since your privacy is important to us, SafeCaller has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.   
This document sets forth the SafeCaller Online Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) for this web site, www.safecaller.com (the “Site”). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Site. 

By visiting this site or downloading the software you confirm and acknowledge that you have read this statement and that you are happy for your data to be used under the terms of this statement. 

_**Your visit data**_  
We store data about your visit like which pages/files on our site you requested on your visit and which pages referred you to our site if your browser sends us that data. We also store the date and time of your visits and information about the frequency of your visits to our site in order to improve our marketing and also for fraud prevention. 

_**Links to other sites**_  
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SafeCaller Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours.  
Our Privacy Statement applies solely to [www.safecaller.com](http://www.safecaller.com/). 

_**Opt-Out policy**_  
When a visitor registers, the visitor will be given the opportunity to select whether or not to be included in the SafeCaller Software mailing/fax list. Inclusion on the mailing list may entitle the user to receive information or updates about special offers, programs, new products and/or services. Choosing not to register means the user will not be able to receive these benefits or this information. 

_**Use of Cookies**_  
When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we use “‘cookies” to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, and enables SafeCaller to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.) 

_**Personal Data**_  
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing software applications, SafeCaller may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, SafeCaller may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

To help us improve our privacy policies, please give us your feedback, comments and suggestions.
